If you use coding
agents, you've been hearing a lot about context management,
and you've probably noticed how tedious and imprecise it can be.
And that's because really, it feels like more of an art than a science.
These days, we're kind of just sharing around markdown documents.
We're not really checking to see if they improve our agent's behaviour or not.
It's very vibes based, and that's okay, because the ecosystem
is moving really quickly.
But I think it's time that we start treating this context
as a first class primitive in our software and in our processes.
And that's really where Tessl comes in.
So Tessl allows you to version context, to share context
and to evaluate it to see if it's actually improving agent behaviour.
So let's talk about how we eval your context.
We do three types of evals in the product today.
Task evals, skill review and repo evals.
Task evals are about evaluating agent behaviour with and without your context.
So we develop scenarios based on your context
and then see how the agent behaves with and without it.
This is really not about the content of your context.
It's about how it affects agent behaviour.
Skill review.
It's a little cheeky to call this an eval.
I think of this more as skill linting.
So we've encoded a bunch of skill writing
best practices from Anthropic and other sources.
And we're just evaluating the actual content of your skill
for how well it's written and how well it conforms to those best practices.
So for repo evals we are generating
realistic scenarios based on recent commit history.
And we're seeing how your agent fares in that environment
with and without your context and scoring the results.
Of course.
You know, if you've run any type of eval before that there's variance to deal with.
LLMs and agent behaviour are non-deterministic.
So we've done a lot of the work for you around normalising
those scores excluding crazy outliers.
Really we've done a lot of the thinking around
how to make this as easy as possible Evals are important
because otherwise context is just markdown.
You can get started for free at tessl.io/registry.